# LX Jordon Bobo (801) 386-3402 Millcreek, UT. 84124 iordon.bobo@outlook.com

github.com/JordonBobo linkedin.com/in/jordon-bobo/

#### Summary

#### jordonbobo.github.io/Portfolio

2+ years' experience developing and maintaining computer scripts. Strong analytic skills that made it possible to adhere to federal compliance standards in systems with protected information. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Programming from the University of Utah.

Technical Skills **JavaScript** MySQL MongoDB Node.JS ReactJS HTML/CSS Bootstrap GitHub

#### Projects

#### Middle Earth Supplier

middleearthsupplier.herokuapp.com

Collaboration with 3 other programmers to build an online retail website with fictional products to demonstrate functionality and style. Has an employee section which requires a login to access. My primary contributions were the UX/UI.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/MiddleEarthSupplier

Tools used: Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize, Express, Node, GSAP, Bootstrap, ¡Query

**Travel Quiz** jordonbobo.github.io/JSQuiz02-Travel/

A small fun quiz app that lets users answer questions to get travel suggestions. Built for mobile or desktop users.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/JSQuiz02-Travel Tools used: JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap

#### Alpha Investments

iordonbobo.github.io/AlphaInvestments/

An investing website that shows company information, stock performance, and current news headlines for publicly traded US companies. Collaboration project with 4 other programmers.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/AlphaInvestments Chart.is, Ajax, Alpha Vantage API, NYTimes API Tools used:

### Experience

Utah Higher Education Assistance Authority (UHEAA). Salt Lake City, UT.

## **Systems Support Specialist**

May 2019 - Feb 2021

- Extensive multitasking in order to complete overlapping projects and tasks without overlooking any key system or variable.
- Fostered a collaboration focused environment to develop, maintain, and improve inhouse software.

**Processor** Dec 2017 - May 2019

Exceeded all expected accomplishment standards by more than 20% with the lowest number of quality assurance issues in the department.

# Murray City Corporation. Murray, UT

# **Library Services Aide**

Nov 2013 – July 2017

- Facilitated the library's acquisition and implementation of new ILS software and Self Service Machines.
- Administered meetings which concluded how to best utilize \$50,000+ annual capital expenditures budget.

## Education

## **University of Utah Coding Bootcamp**

Nov 2020 - June 2021

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

#### **Utah State University.**

Graduated May 2013

Bachelor of Arts in History